A Guide to the John Redd Hutcheson Papers, 1917-1962
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Personal Papers
  - Hutcheson, Eleanor, 1941-57 (Box 9, Folder 363)
  - Hutcheson Hall Dedication, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 364)
  - Hutcheson, Henry and Family, 1924-56 (Box 9, Folder 365)
  - Hutcheson, Jesse, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 366)
  - Hutcheson, Joel, 1938-55 (Box 9, Folder 367)
  - Hutcheson, John L., 1949-50 (Box 9, Folder 368)
  - Hutcheson Jr., John R., 1942-61 (Box 9, Folder 369)
  - Hutcheson, Lucy, 1945-59 (Box 9, Folder 370)
  - Hutcheson, Richard and Family, 1924-59 (Box 9, Folder 371)
  - Hutcheson Sr., Robert F., 1917-40 (Box 9, Folder 372)
  - Hutcheson, Robert P., 1944-45 (Box 9, Folder 373)
  - Hutcheson, Rosilie, 1951-60 (Box 9, Folder 374)
  - Hutcheson, Sterling, 1957-59 (Box 9, Folder 375)
    - includes a Virginia court ruling on desegregation of public schools
  - Hutcheson Jr., T.B., 1943-62 (Box 9, Folder 376)
  - Hutcheson Sr., T.B., 1923-50 (Box 9, Folder 377)
  - Hutcheson Sr., T.B., Death of, 1950-51 (Box 9, Folder 378)
  - Hutcheson Family-Miscellaneous, 1956-61 (Box 9, Folder 379)
  - Hutchinson, John D., 1956-58 (Box 9, Folder 380)
    - includes descussion of John Redd Hutcheson's family owning slaves and desegregation of public schools in Virginia
  - Illness, 1924-59 (Box 9, Folder 381)
  - Injury at farm, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 382)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1960-62 (Box 9, Folder 383)
  - International Harvester Company, 1955-58 (Box 9, Folder 384)
  - Investors Syndicate, 1939-54 (Box 9, Folder 385)
  - Irrigation, 1957-58 (Box 9, Folder 386)
  - J-Miscellaneous, 1945-60 (Box 9, Folder 387)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital, 1954-55 (Box 9, Folder 388)
  - K-Miscellaneous, 1919-61 (Box 9, Folder 389)
  - Kelly, John A., 1950-51 (Box 9, Folder 390)
  - L-Miscellaneous, 1947-60 (Box 9, Folder 391)
  - Letters of Congratulations, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 392)
  - Letters of Congratulations, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 393)
  - Love Property, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 394)
  - M-Miscellaneous, 1933-61 (Box 9, Folder 395)
  - Martin, John, 1924-38 (Box 9, Folder 396)
  - Memorial Chapel, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 397)
  - Milk Commission, 1935-61 (Box 9, Folder 398)
  - Miller, A.W., 1927-40 (Box 9, Folder 399)
  - Miller, Ledford, and Pierce, 1950-53 (Box 9, Folder 400)
  - Montgomery Mutual Insurance Agency, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 401)
  - Moore, Ike and Joe and Families, 1948-61 (Box 10, Folder 402)
  - Moore Property, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 403)
  - Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1927-50 (Box 10, Folder 404)
  - N-Miscellaneous, 1943-62 (Box 10, Folder 405)
  - New York Life Insurance, 1933-59 (Box 10, Folder 406)
  - Nichols Farm Supply, 1956-59 (Box 10, Folder 407)
  - O-Miscellaneous, 1923-58 (Box 10, Folder 408)
  - P-Miscellaneous, 1934-61 (Box 10, Folder 409)
  - Parrott, Francis, 1926-47 (Box 10, Folder 410)
  - Patrick Henry Memorial Foundation, 1945-58 (Box 10, Folder 411)
  - Peanut Growers Association, 1921-37 (Box 10, Folder 412)
  - Pierce Insurance Agency, 1940-62 (Box 10, Folder 413)
  - Pittsylvania Tobacco Growers Association, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 414)
    - the PTGA lodged a complaint against Hutcheson and tried to gather public support in an unsuccessful attempt to get him removed as director of the Extension Service
  - Powell, Everett and Napoleon, 1935-51 (Box 10, Folder 415)
  - Presbyterian Church, 1924-53 (Box 10, Folder 416)
  - Presbyterian Church, 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 417)
  - Presbyterian Church, 1956-61 (Box 10, Folder 418)
  - Printing Department, 1945-62 (Box 10, Folder 419)
  - Progressive Farmer Magazine, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 420)
  - Quinn, I.T., 1952 (Box 10, Folder 421)
  - R-Miscellaneous, 1925-61 (Box 10, Folder 422)
  - Readers Digest, 1949-58 (Box 10, Folder 423)
  - Redd, Carter, 1942-52 (Box 10, Folder 424)
  - Redd, Cora, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 425)
  - Redd, H.B., 1945-59 (Box 10, Folder 426)
  - Retirement, 1944-59 (Box 10, Folder 427)
  - Rice, C.T., 1935-48 (Box 10, Folder 428)
  - Rockingham Poultry Marketing Cooperative, 1945-49 (Box 10, Folder 429)
  - Rotary Club, 1923-61 (Box 10, Folder 430)
  - S-Miscellaneous, 1944-60 (Box 10, Folder 431)
  - Smith-Douglas Company, 1952-61 (Box 10, Folder 432)
  - Smith, Kate, 1932-57 (Box 10, Folder 433)
  - Social Security, 1951-62 (Box 10, Folder 434)
  - Soil Conservation Service, 1956-59 (Box 10, Folder 435)
  - Sons of the American Revolution, 1946-51 (Box 10, Folder 436)
  - Southern Railway, 1942-56 (Box 10, Folder 437)
  - Southern States Cooperative, 1933-57 (Box 10, Folder 438)
  - Southern States Cooperative, 1958-59 (Box 10, Folder 439)
  - Southern States Cooperative, 1959-61 (Box 10, Folder 440)
  - Speech Materials, 1928-54 (Box 10, Folder 441)
  - Speech Materials, 1955-56 (Box 10, Folder 442)
  - Speech Materials, 1957-58 (Box 10, Folder 443)
  - Speeches, 1922-46 (Box 10, Folder 444)
  - Speeches, 1947-49 (Box 10, Folder 445)
  - Speeches, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 446)
  - Speeches, 1951-52 (Box 11, Folder 447)
  - Speeches, 1953-55 (Box 11, Folder 448)
  - Speeches, 1956-57 (Box 11, Folder 449)
  - Speeches, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 450)
  - State Farm Mutual Auto Insurance, 1937-51 (Box 11, Folder 451)
  - Stephens, Calvin, 1956-59 (Box 11, Folder 452)
  - Stock Transactions, 1950-58 (Box 11, Folder 453)
  - Swink, H.W., 1949-52 (Box 11, Folder 454)
  - T-Miscellaneous, 1939-61 (Box 11, Folder 455)
  - Taxes, 1918-39 (Box 11, Folder 456)
  - Taxes, 1940-50 (Box 11, Folder 457)
  - Taxes, 1951-59 (Box 11, Folder 458)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, 1923-47 (Box 11, Folder 459)
  - Thomas, Harriet, 1955-57 (Box 11, Folder 460)
  - Thompson, W.H., 1955-57 (Box 11, Folder 461)
  - Thompson, W.H., 1958-59 (Box 11, Folder 462)
  - Thompson, W.H., 1960 (Box 11, Folder 463)
  - Thompson, W.H., 1961-62 (Box 11, Folder 464)
  - Tobacco Growers Association, 1923-25 (Box 11, Folder 465)
  - Treasurer of Virginia Tech, 1946-57 (Box 11, Folder 466)
  - U-Miscellaneous, 1954-59 (Box 11, Folder 467)
  - Union Theological Seminary, 1949-59 (Box 11, Folder 468)
  - United States Civil Service, 1929-62 (Box 11, Folder 469)
  - V-Miscellaneous, 1937-60 (Box 11, Folder 470)
  - Veterans Insurance, 1919-56 (Box 11, Folder 471)
  - Veterinary Services, 1955-60 (Box 11, Folder 472)
  - Virginia Farm Bureau Mutual Insurance Company, 1951-59 (Box 11, Folder 473)
  - Virginia Forest Service, 1957-58 (Box 11, Folder 474)
  - W-Miscellaneous, 1923-60 (Box 11, Folder 475)
  - Wilson, M.O., 1926-35 (Box 11, Folder 476)
  - Wilson, M.O., 1936-51 (Box 11, Folder 477)
  - Wooding, N.H. and Family, 1937-61 (Box 11, Folder 478)
  - World War I Memorial Building Fund, 1922-23 (Box 11, Folder 479)
  - World War I Military Service, 1918 (Box 11, Folder 480)
  - Y-Miscellaneous, 1945-54 (Box 11, Folder 481)
  - Scrapbook, 1927-32 (Box 12)
  - The Breeder's Gazette, 1899-1900 (Box 13)